We sell performance marketing and demand generation services.
So we do $2 million per year in revenue.
We'd like to be at 10 million.
How many customers do you have right now?
Like 40.
Okay, are you doing with SMBs?
No, most of them are like mid-size.
You probably mispriced.
So it seems like you've moved up in Avatar.
You just didn't match it with price, that's all.
Correct, we've gone up market, but-
Just forgot to change your price.
You know, we closed 15K a month the other day
and they weren't even batting an eye, actually.
Yeah, which means you undercharged.
You're probably losing people who are legit
because you're too cheap.
You're bordering on so cheap for a mid-market company
that they don't believe that you're legit enough.